보자, 레이첼은 머핀에
에스프레소, 4달러 50센트
Okay, Rach, that's muffin
and espresso, $4.50.
로스는 더블 라테
2달러 75센트
Ross, double latte, $2.75.
Chandler, coffee and a scone, $4.25.
챈들러는 커피랑 핫케이크
4달러 25센트
피비의 허브티는
1달러 25센트
And Phoebe, herbal tea, $1.25.
자, 그럼 합이...
All together that's $12.75.
12달러 75센트
쟤 전화요금 80달러도
반으로 못 나누던 애 맞아?
This coming from the man who couldn't
split our $80 phone bill in half.
- 안녕하세요
- 네
How much do I owe you?
머핀 하나에 라테면 얼마죠?
조이 트리비아니 씨가
공짜로 드리는 겁니다
That's on the house,
courtesy of Joey Tribbiani.
저런, 고맙다고 전해주세요
Great. Well, tell him thanks.
조이란 사람 왠지
괜찮은 남자 같은데
And since Joey seems like
such a nice guy...
언제 만날 수 있을까요?
maybe we could go out?
글쎄요
He's not used to women
being so forward...
그 친구가 적극적인 여성을
좋아하는지 모르겠지만
but I could check with him.
He says it's okay.
한번 물어나 보죠...
그렇게 하자는군요
네, 감사합니다
안녕히 가세요
Great. Thanks. Bye-bye.
조이, 왜 우린 공짜로 안 줘?
How come our stuff isn't free?
공짜 먹고 싶으면
꽉 끼는 치마 입고 와
It will be when you look like
that in a tight skirt.
죽이는 걸? 여자들
진짜 많이 꼬인다
I'm getting more dates than ever.
잠깐, 예쁜 여자한테만
공짜로 주는 거야?
You're only giving free stuff
to the pretty girls?
너 진짜 밥맛이다
Joey, that is so gross!
공짜 핫케이크 하나
드릴까, 아가씨?
How about a scone on the house, baby?
보는 눈은 있어설랑
I'm pretty.
The One With Rachel's Sister
-Hey, does anyone have any gum?
-I do.
누구 껌 있냐?
여기
들고 있어, 미안
Here. Sorry.
어디 보자
Oh, you know what?
No.
아니네
Wait a second.
기다려봐
- 여기 어디 있을 텐데
- 됐다, 그만둬라
-I know it's in here.
-You know what? I'm good.
미안, 대짜 백이라
있는 줄 알았어
Sorry, I guess it's in my big bag.
Say, does anybody have a goldfish?
누구 금붕어 있냐?
- 나야
- 그래
근무시간일 텐데 웬일이야?
Why are you here?
Shouldn't you be at work?
퇴근하라잖아
They sent me home.
They said I can't work if I'm sick.
아프면 가서 쉬래
저런
- 아프면 어떡해
- 안 아파
-Sorry you're sick.
-I'm not sick!
난 병 안 걸려
I don't get sick. Getting sick is
for weaklings, it's for pansies.
계집애처럼 약해 빠진
애들이나 병에 걸리지
No one thinks that you're a pansy...
너 약골 아닌 건 알지만
but we do think
that you need a tissue.
콧물이나 좀 닦아라
난 3년 동안 한 번도
안 아팠어
I have not been sick
in over three years.
아픈 게 확실하네
이건 네 코 안에 있던 거야
I think you're sick because
that used to be in your nose.
I'll get tissue.
휴지 갖다 줄게
휴지 필요 없어
난 '멀쩌게'
I don't need a tissue. I'm fine-d.
'멀쩡해'를 '멀쩌게'로 발음하면
When you put a D
at the end of fine...
멀쩡하지 않다는 거야
you're not fine.
난 멀쩌게
I'm fine-d.
원래 발음하기 힘든 단어야
It's a really hard word to say.
- 누구시죠?
- 안녕하세요
-Yes?
-Hi. Is Rachel here? I'm her sister.
레이첼 언니 있나요?
동생 되는데
어머나, 질
Oh, my God, Jill!
어머나, 언니
Oh, my God, Rachel!
어머나, 소개 좀 시켜줄래?
Oh, my God, introduce us.
- 여긴 챈들러
- 안녕하세요
This is Chandler.
And you know Monica and Ross.
- 모니카랑 로스는 알지?
- 안녕, 질
저쪽은 피비, 그리고 조이
And that's Phoebe.
And that's Joey.
안녕하쇼
-How you doing?
-Don't!
하지 마!
여긴 어쩐 일이야?
Honey, what are you doing here?
어떤 동생인지 알겠어?
응석받이? 개망나니?
Which sister is this?
Is this the spoiled one
or the one that bit her?
아빠가 날 호적에서 파버리겠대
Daddy cut me off.
됐다, 감 잡았어
Never mind, I got it.
You know what I said?
그래서 내가 뭐랬는지 알아?
'변호사 고용해서 아빠 재산
몽땅 뺏고 내 손으로 호적 파죠'
I said, "I'll hire a lawyer,
sue you, take all your money...
and cut you off!"
그랬더니 아빠가 뭐래?
Wow. What did he say?
변호사 비용 못 대주겠대
That he wouldn't pay
for my lawyer.
당신의 가장 기특한 딸한테 가서
돈의 소중함을 배우고 오라잖아
Then he told me to learn
the value of money...
from the one daughter
he's actually proud of.
뜨아...
들었냐?
내가 기특하대
Did you hear that?
My dad's proud of me.
기특한 딸이야
- 레이첼
- 그래, 미안
-Rach?
-Oh, yeah. Sorry.
너 무슨 짓을 했기에
호적까지 파버린대?
Honey, so what did you do
that made Dad cut you off?
보트를 샀거든
Okay, I bought a boat.
보트를 사?
You bought a boat?
그냥 친구 주려고 산 거야
It wasn't for me,
it was for a friend.
동생을 친구 삼을 걸 그랬네
Boy, did we make friends
with the wrong sister.
I knew it was stupid and
I shouldn't have done it...
바보짓이라는 건
나도 잘 알지만
but she bought me all these CDs
and said I had a cute haircut.
걔는 CD세트를 사주면서
내 머리모양이 예쁘댔어
근데 아버님께서
이해를 못하셨다?
And your daddy didn't understand?
I know, and usually I just cry
and say I'm sorry and he forgives me.
그러게요, 울면서 잘못했다고
빌면 보통 용서해주시는데
Oh, yes, good criers, the Green girls.
맞아, 그린 여인네들
우는 실력 일품이지
그니까 내 말은
그린 자매란 뜻이야
I mean, the Green sisters.
Man, no matter how you say it...
어떻게 표현을 해도
그린 집안 얘기구나
it still sounds like you're
talking about green people.
진퇴양난이로세
I'm at rock bottom.
아냐, 오히려 너한텐
잘된 일인지도 몰라
This is the best thing that
could've happened to you.
You've needed to get out on your own.
아무튼 언젠가는 독립해야지
When I did it, at first I was scared,
but then look at me now.
나도 처음엔 막막하고
두려웠는데 지금은 봐
아빠한테 하나뿐인
기특한 딸이 됐잖아
I am the only daughter
that Dad is proud of.
정말 너무해, 난 돈도
쓰지 말고 살라는 거야?
I can't believe him.
How does he expect me to buy stuff?
당분간 돈은
안 쓰는 게 좋겠다
Maybe, you know, you
won't buy stuff for a while.
무슨 말씀이실까?
I don't understand.
좋아, 너도 우선은
일자리를 찾은 다음
This is what you'll do.
You're gonna get a job.
You're gonna get an apartment.
살 집을 마련하고
And then you will live off
the money that you earn.
네가 번 돈으로
살아가는 거야
Okay, I know this is what you did...
알았어
언니는 그랬겠지만
but that doesn't sound like me.
그건 나답지 않아
너도 충분히 할 수 있어
Okay, but it can be. It can be you.
내가 도와줄게, 당분간
함께 살자, 그래도 되지?
And you can stay with us.
Right, Phoebe?
그럼, 괜찮아
-Of course, yeah.
-Oh, that's so great!
정말 고마워요
Okay, I'm really gonna do this.
I don't know how to thank you.
그래, 한번 해볼게
이 신세를 어떻게 갚죠?
Oh, I like cars.
난 자동차 좋아해요
-You all finished?
-Yes.
다 드셨나요?
- 네
- 알겠습니다
Great.
자, 오늘 아침 팁이야
Okay, here are the tips
for this morning.
젠은 50달러, 나도 50달러
자넨 8달러 내놔야겠어
Jen gets 50, 50 for me
and Joey owes 8 dollars.
네?
-What?
-For all the free food you gave away.
공짜 음식 돌렸잖아
공짜 음식인데
왜 내가 돈을 내요?
If it's free, how come
you're charging me for it?
누구 생일이 아니면
공짜 음식 안 나가
We don't give anything away
unless it's a birthday.
모델 콘테스트
3위 입상자 정도면?
What if they came in third
in a modeling contest?
안 돼
No.
죄송합니다
Sorry.
오늘 정말 힘들었어
I just had the hardest day.
Some of these are so heavy.
짐은 왜 이렇게 무거워
이건 무슨 돈으로 샀어?
신용카드는 다 뺏겼다면서
How did you pay? I thought
your dad took your credit card.
I memorized those numbers
when I was 15.
카드번호 정도야
15살 때부터 줄줄 뀄지
독립하려고 준비한 거야
But look at all the cool
make-it-on-my-own stuff I got!
먼저 이건...
'채용해주세요' 스웨터
This is my "Please hire me" sweater.
그리고 이건...
'이 아파트 세주세요' 바지
And these are my "Don't you want
to rent me this apartment?" pants.
아빠한테 옷값을 떠넘기는 게
독립하려는 자세는 아닐 텐데
Charging clothes to your dad doesn't
qualify as making it on your own.
그 과학자 오빠
참 깐깐하시네
Oh, Mr. Scientist has to get
all technical.
레이첼도 좋아하진 않을 거야
Rachel's not gonna think
it's a good idea.
언니가 여왕이라도 돼요?
-So who made her queen of the world?
-I would love that job!
여왕 좋지
얘들아
- 뭐하는 거야?
- 언니 왔구나
What's going on?
질
Jill!
너 쇼핑했어?
Did you shop?
아니
No.
오빠랑 언니가
They did.
그래, 우리 쇼핑했어
Yeah, we went shopping!
너희가 쇼핑을 했다고?
You went shopping?
이제야 맘 잡고 살아보려는
애 앞에서 잘들 하는 짓이다
Then you came here
and paraded it under Jill's nose...
when you know she's trying to quit.
That's terrible.
너희 정말 못됐어
- 미안해, 질
- 미안하다
Sorry, Jill.
뭘 샀는데?
So, what'd you get?
응, 난 저기...
Oh, well, all right. Thank you.
I got this, you know,
"I want a job" sweater.
'일자리가 필요해' 스웨터
그리고 이건...
And then I got..
These are apartment pants.
아파트 바지
아파트 바지?
Apartment pants?
왜, 들어본 적 없어?
You've never heard of them?
물론 들어봤지
Of course I've heard of them.
로스, 넌 뭘 샀니?
Ross, what'd you get?
난 이거...
I got this...
바로 이거
This.
파시미나?
-A pashmina?
-Yeah!
응
나 이거 무지 좋아하거든
I love these babies.
정말?
Really?
로스, 파시미나가 뭔데?
What's a pashmina?
깔개
It's a rug.
질
Jill?
미안해, 언니
I'm sorry, Rachel.
그게 나한테 통할 줄 알아?
내가 개발한 거야
You think that's gonna work on me?
I invented that.
참, 그랬지
Right! But I am sorry.
하여튼 미안해
좋아, 실수는 한 번으로 족해
다신 이런 일 없도록, 알았지?
It's okay.
One little setback is okay.
-But don't let it happen again, okay?
-Okay.
그래
다 아빠 돈으로 산 거니까
내가 다 압수해야겠지만
Now, since Daddy paid for all this
stuff, I should take it all away.
인정상...
파시미나 숄만 가져갈게
But I'm just gonna take the pashmina.
그리고 이 바지랑
And the pants.
그냥 다 가져가야겠다
그래야 정신 바짝 차리지
I'll take it all, because that way,
you'll learn the lesson.
좋아
Alrighty.
난 가볼 데가 있으니까
이따 저녁 때 보자
I'm gonna run a couple of errands
and I will see you at dinner.
몽땅 뺏겼어
She took all my stuff.
그래
Yeah. Everything but
the little blue one.
이 조그만 녀석만 빼고
그게 제일 좋은 건데
That's the best one!
세상에, 정말 고마워
Oh, my God. Thank you so much!
뭐 그런 걸 갖고...
Well, hey.
세상에, 답답하긴
파시미나를 깔개라니
Oh, my gosh, that was so lame.
Like a pashmina could be a rug.
그러는 넌 어떻고?
Oh, yeah? How about you
with the "I'm sorry"?
'미안해'
그만해, 내가 언제 그랬어
Shut up! I wasn't like that at all.
난 아파트 바지라고 했잖아
정말 푼수 같지?
What about what I said about
the apartment pants? How dumb was l?
학생 때도 이렇게 귀여웠어요?
-Were you this cute in high school?
-Oh, stop.
그만해
- 오빠나 그만해
- 아니, 너나 그만해
-No, you stop.
오빠가 그만해
좋아, 내가 중간에
앉을 테니까 둘 다 그만해
Why don't I sit here
and then you'll both stop it?
그래, 내가 뭘 하면 좋겠어?
Okay. So, what do you want to do?
뭔가 쇼킹한 걸 해보자
Let's do something crazy.
그럼 휴식을 취하면서
음료수 진땅 마시는 거야
I know, let's rest and drink
lots of fluids.
알았어, 쉴게
Okay, I'll rest.
하지만 내가 침대로 가면
너도 따라올 거지?
But if I'm going to bed,
then you're coming with me.
거부하기 꽤 힘들겠는걸?
콧물만 흐르지 않으면
See, that would be impossible
to resist if you weren't all...
drippy here.
그래서 지금 이걸
사양한다 이거야?
Are you saying that you don't
want to get with this?
행여 멀쩡할 때라도
그런 건 하지 마라
I don't think you should say that
even when you're healthy.
어서
Come on.
서운해 할 거 없어
어떻게 환자하고 섹스를 해
Don't take this personally.
I just can't have sex
with a sick person.
맞는 말이야
I'm with you. I can't have sex with
a sick person either. Disgusting!
환자랑 섹스를 하다니
생각만 해도 역겨워
하지만 난 환자 아냐
증명할 기회를 줘봐
But I'm not sick!
Let me prove it to you.
우린 전성기를 맞은
신체 건강한 남녀야
We are two healthy people
in the prime of lime.
바로 그거야, 난 이 전성기를
끝내고 싶지 않아
See, that's the thing, I would like
to stay in the "prime of lime."
Oh, okay, now I'll do it.
좋아, 그럼 하자
왔니?
무슨 일 있어?
Hey. What's up?
I think there's something
you should know.
너한테 알려줄 게 있어서
아파트 바지 얘기면 됐어
Better not be about
the apartment pants.
I just pitched the idea to my boss
at Ralph Lauren and she loved it.
부장님한테 그 얘기했더니
엄청 좋아하시더라
아냐, 너 나간 다음에 내가
로스랑 질하고 같이 있었잖아
No. It's just, I was...
I was with Ross and Jill
after you left...
걔들 눈 맞은 것 같아
and I'm pretty sure I saw
a little spark between them.
뭐?
-What?
-I mean, it's probably nothing.
별거 아닌지도 모르지만
But I wanted to warn you
that there might be something.
뭔가 있는 것 같으니까
조심하라는 뜻이야
- 로스하고 질이?
- 그래
-With Ross and Jill?
-Yeah.
로스랑 내 동생이?
With Ross and my sister?
응
내 동생 질이랑
옛날 남자친구 로스가?
With my sister Jill
and my ex-boyfriend Ross?
그렇대도
- 그럴 리가 없어
- 그럼 됐네
-Oh, there is no way.
-Okay, then.
세상에, 미치고 팔짝 뛰겠네
Oh, my God! I cannot believe that!
로스가 다른 여자 만나는 것도
싫은데 하물며 내 동생이라니
I don't like it when he dates anyone,
but my sister?
이거 근친상간 아냐?
Isn't that incest or something?
둘이 섹스라도 하면 어쩌지?
And they're gonna have sex.
그러다 결혼이라도 하면?
Oh, no! What if he marries her too?
정말 기가 막힐 일이다
This is just terrible.
난 막을 수도 없어
로스는 내 남자가 아니잖아
And I can't stop it.
I don't own Ross.
질이야 걸리는 게 없으니까
자기 하고 싶은 대로 하겠지
And Jill should be able to do
what she wants to do.
Oh, my God, I can't believe Ross
is marrying my little sister.
맙소사, 로스랑
내 동생이 결혼을 해?
이런 끔찍한 일이 생기다니
This is the worst thing that
could've ever happened to me.
그래도 아파트 바지는 잘됐잖아
But great news about
the apartment pants, huh?
3달러 85센트입니다
That'll be $3.85.
무슨 소리예요?
What? Yesterday you said
I was too pretty to pay.
어젠 내가 예뻐서
공짜라고 했잖아요
안 되겠어요, 주인장께서...
It's just, I can't,
because my manager said that I..
생일 축하합니다
Happy birthday to you
사랑하는 애니의...
-Happy birthday, dear Annie..
-Amy!
- 에이미
- 에이미의...
Amy
생일 축하합니다
Happy birthday to you
그거 참 신기하네요
나도 오늘 생일인데
That's weird,
today's my birthday too.
딴 데 가서 알아보세요
Not in here, it isn't.
늦어서 미안해
무슨 일인데?
Sorry I'm late. What's up?
왔니?
일자리 구하는 건
잘돼가나 궁금해서
I just wanted to see if there were
any leads on the old job front.
No. But I walked past three sales
and didn't go in.
아니, 근데 방금 세일 가게를
세 개나 지나쳐왔어
나 대단하지?
How strong am I?
장하다
That is great.
진짜 탄탄한 일자리를
가진 애는 로스야
You know who doesn't have to
job-hunt? Ross.
걘 대학에 있잖아
-He works at the university.
-Yeah?
근데?
너희끼리 그 얘기를 했을 거고
곧 데이트도 할 생각이겠지?
So you guys talked? So you get along?
So you're gonna go out?
나랑 로스 오빠가?
Me go out with Ross? No.
말도 안 돼
왜 그런 생각을 했어?
God, no.
What would make you think that?
피비가 그러잖아
Phoebe...
너희 둘 사이가
심상치 않다면서
said she thought she saw something
between you guys.
- 아냐, 좋은 사람이긴 하지
- 그래
I mean, he's nice.
친구로서는 괜찮지만
사귈 만한 남자는 아냐
He's the kind you're friends with,
but not the kind you date.
언니나 되니까
그런 남자를 만났지
He's the kind you date,
because you did. But me?
난...
Not so much.
그런 짓 안 해
그런 짓은 안 해?
Oh, not so much. What do you mean?
Is there something wrong with Ross?
무슨 뜻이야? 로스한테
무슨 문제라도 있어?
No, no, no. He's just...
아니, 그냥...
글쎄, 약간...
I don't know.
You know, he's just a little bookish.
책벌레 같잖아
폐인이란 말이니?
Are you saying he's a geek?
언니가 보기에도 그래?
You think so too?
아냐, 로스가 무슨 폐인이야
No. Ross is not a geek.
좋아, 그냥 내 취향이
아니라고 해 두지 뭐
Then let's just say
he's not my type.
핸섬한 게 네 취향이 아냐?
Handsome is not your type?
똑똑하고 자상하고 키스도
잘하는데 그런 게 싫다고?
Smart, kind, good kisser.
What, those things aren't
on your list?
로스는 정말 괜찮은 애야
잘하면 봉 잡는 거라고
Ross is great.
You'd be lucky to be with him.
알았어, 그렇게 멋진 사람이면
만나자고 해볼게
If it means that much,
then I'll ask him out.
얘가 왜 이래
그런 뜻이 아냐
Oh, no. That's not what I meant.
아니, 언니 말이 맞는 거 같아
You know what? You're right.
나한테 정말 잘해줬거든
He has been really nice to me.
하지만 네 취향이 아니잖아
Yeah, but he's not your type.
그게 좋을 수도 있어
But maybe that's good.
이제 새 인생을 시작하는데
폐인도 한번 만나보지 뭐
I'm doing all these different things.
Maybe I should just try
dating a geek too.
그래도 너무 서두르진 마라
Yeah, but you don't want
to try too much too fast.
서두르기만 하던 여자애가
어떻게 됐는지 기억 안 나?
You remember what happened
to the little girl who...
tried too much too fast, don't you?
어떻게 됐는데?
What?
그만 죽어버렸어
She died, Jill.
챈들러
Chandler!
What is it, honey?
You need some tea? Some soup?
왜 그래, 자기야?
차나 수프 만들어줄까?
Calling Dr. Big.
변강쇠 오빠 호출이오
침대로 올라오세요
Dr. Big to the bed.
Jeez, honey,
I thought you were asleep.
왜 이래, 자기야
자고 있는 줄 알았더니
어떻게 잠이 오겠어?
자기가 옆방에 있는데
How could I be asleep knowing
that you were in the next room?
난 자고 있었어
I was asleep.
안 돼, 섹시한 게 뭔지 알아?
No, honey. You know what's sexy?
Layers.
- 옷이야
- 안 돼
옷이 섹시하고
담요가 섹시하고
Layers are sexy.
And blankets are sexy.
And hot-water bottles are sexy.
참, 뜨거운 물주머니도 섹시해
어서 침대로 들어와
난 아무렇지도 않아
Get into bed.
I want to prove I'm not sick.
지금 내 기분을
자기도 느끼게 해줄게
I want to make you feel
as good as I feel.
제발 얌전히 쉬고 있어
Would you please get some rest?
난 괜찮다니까
I'm fine.
기침하잖아
-You're coughing.
-No, I'm not.
아냐, 웃는 거야
No, I'm not, I'm laughing.
- 뭐가 웃겨서?
- 방금 네가 한 말
-At what?
-Just something I heard before.
-Tell me.
-No, I don't want it to spoil the mood.
뭔데?
얘기 안 할래
분위기 망가지잖아
생일 축하합니다
Happy birthday to you
-You're paying for that.
-No, it's her birthday.
자네가 계산해
아뇨, 진짜 생일이래요
You've sung "Happy Birthday"
to 20 women today.
오늘만 생일축가 스무 번째야
- 하지만 진짜로...
- 이제 생일 머핀 돌리지 마
You are no longer authorized
to distribute birthday muffins.
젠장!
Damn it!
레이첼
- 나야
- 그래
혹시 동생한테 날
사귀어보라고 했니?
Did you tell your sister
to ask me out?
-Well, yeah.
-Oh, wow! I mean, wow.
그래
와우! 이건... 와우다!
I think she's cute, but...
귀엽다고 생각은 했었지만
I never would've thought of
going out with her. Never!
따로 만난다는 생각은
꿈에도 못해봤거든
Really?
정말이야?
근데 네 얘길 듣고 보니
못할 것도 없겠더라
But after you said it's okay,
I figured, "Why not?"
그럼 마음에는 있었네
Oh, so not really "never."
I have to say you are
a much bigger person than I am.
어쨌든 넌 나보다
훨씬 그릇이 커
I mean, after all we've been through.
난 우리가 그렇게 되고 나서
I wish I had a brother
to reciprocate.
복수해줄 형제가
있었으면 했거든
너 모니카랑 사귀고 싶으면
내가 적극 밀어줄게
If you ever date Monica,
you have my blessing.
나도 민다
And mine.
Chandler?
챈들러
I think I'm sick.
나 아픈가 봐
Really?
그래?
Struck down in the "pribe of libe."
인생의 전성기가 끝났나?
Okay, fine, I admit it.
I feel terrible.
알았어, 인정할게
상태가 엉망이야
Will you please rub this on my chest?
- 이거 가슴에 좀 발라줄래?
- 그러자
No, no, no.
You are not getting me this way.
안 되지
이런 수법엔 안 넘어가
Come on, I really need your help here.
- 진심으로 얘기하는 거야
- 글쎄 안 된다니까
-Fine, I'll rub it on myself.
-Okay.
- 그럼 내가 바르지 뭐
- 좋으실 대로
So you're just kind of
rubbing it on yourself?
그냥 아무 의미 없이
바르는 거지?
-Yeah.
-It's nice.
그럼
좋다
You kidding me?
Is this turning you on?
장난하는 거야?
지금 자기 흥분돼?
Yes.
그래
말도 안 돼, 뭣 때문에?
내 모습이? 아님 냄새가?
Is it the rubbing or the smell?
It's all very, very good.
둘 다 너무 좋아
So you want to go...
그럼 우리...
mix it up?
해볼까?
-Not now, I'm sick.
-Oh, come on, you big faker!
지금은 안 돼
나 아프잖아
맘에 없는 소리 집어치우고
아픈 사람하고는
절대 안 잔다면서
What about never sleeping
with sick people?
Well, that was before
all the vaporizing action.
그건 자기가 야리꾸리한
자태를 보이기 전이지
- 좋아, 정 원한다면 뭐
- 그렇지
Okay, if you really
want to have sex.
마법의 주문이네
Worked like a charm.
나야
그래, 여긴 웬일이야?
Why are you here?
This is where Ross and I are meeting
for our date. So, what do you think?
로스 오빠랑 여기서
만나기로 했거든
자, 나 어때?
I don't like it.
별로 맘에 안 드는데?
-Really?
-It's kind of slutty.
정말?
날라리 같아
It's yours.
언니 옷이야
Yeah, well, I'm a slut.
그래, 나 날라리다
Me too.
나도 그래
- 안녕, 질
- 어서 와
Hi, Jill.
Hi...
안녕...
Rachel.
- 레이첼
You're not at home,
you're right here.
너 집에 안 있고
여기 있었네?
Yeah, I know.
그래
And I bet you thought it would
be weird. But it's not.
이상할 줄 알았겠지만
전혀 아니다
Okay.
좋아
So, well, I'll...
그럼...
자정 전까진 귀가시킬게
I'll have her home by midnight.
왜 아직 안 들어온 거야?
Why aren't you home yet?
Is someone there?
누구 왔니?
Oh, yeah, it's me. Sorry.
나야
미안하다
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐해?
I'm just looking out your window...
그냥 창 밖을 보고 있어
경치 구경
at the view.
What are you guys doing?
너흰 뭐하는데?
We got some vapor rub in some places.
마찰요법을 베풀고 있지
자기 아파트로 데려왔군
He brought her back to his apartment.
Who?
누가?
Is that your sister?
네 동생 아냐?
She is a slut!
날라리 같은 계집애
Ross is on a date with your sister.
How weird is that?
오빠랑 네 동생이 사귀니?
이런 경우가 어디 있어?
Oh, my God, he's taking off
her clothes!
맙소사, 봐
쟤 옷을 벗기고 있어
He's taking off her coat.
코트 받아주는 거잖아
Oh, this is just terrible.
내가 못살겠다
Oh, no, it's not. It's a first date.
I'm sure that nothing is gonna...
아냐, 첫 데이트잖아
장담하지만 별일 없을...
누군 신나겠다
He's gonna get some.
눈부시잖아
Of the glare...
from the streetlight
out of his apartment.
밖에서 불빛이 들어오니깐
You know, so he's closed
the drapes there...
뭐 알다시피...
커튼을 친 이유는
so he can have a nice, pleasant...
네 동생이랑 화기애애한
대화를 나누자는 뜻이겠지
conversation with
your little sister.
Well, I'm off to bed.
난 잠이나 자련다
계속
나 상태가 안 좋아
I don't feel good.
나한테 옮기지 마
You better not get me sick.
과일이나 먹을래
I need some fruit
or some juice or some....
주스라도
아님...
손가락이나 빨까?
Or some nothing.
아무 것도 없어
누가 냉장고 털어 갔지?
There's nothing in here.
Who took our food?
Can I interest you in a slice
of lasagna or a drumstick?
라자냐 어떻습니까
아니면 닭다리?
됐어요
-No, thanks.
-Are you sure? It's on the house.
정말이세요?
그냥 드리는 건데
-No, thanks.
-How about going out with me Friday night?
됐어요
금요일 밤에 만날까요?
-No, thanks.
-What are you gonna do.
할 수 없죠 뭐